# Alexander Marks,



# BSC Profile

People focused team player with advanced analytical, communication and problem solving skills. Recently moved to London after achieving a 2:1 Mathematics and Sports Science degree from Loughborough University. Experienced in coaching and leading teams in both educational and sporting disciplines. Provided private tuition to GCSE and A level mathematics students and served as Loughborough University Golf Club Captain during 2017/18, achieving a ranking of 3rd best club in the country. 2020 club champion at one of the highest ranked golf clubs in the country.

## **Employment**

#### Summer 2017 - Summer 2019 | Barman | Manor House Inn, Croyde

- Managerial role supervising other staff and completing the pub closure procedures
- Customer focused role requiring ability to create a rapport with a range of people, and provide outstanding customer service

#### February 2018 | Cricket Trader | ioSport

• Adjusting live betting prices, accurately and swiftly scoring the events of a cricket match and working with other traders to give them information quickly

#### February 2015 - July 2016 | Maths Tutor | Braunton Academy

- Primarily helping Year 11 students prepare for their GCSE exams with a focus on improving outcomes for these students
- Tutoring younger students of varying abilities, providing motivation for underperforming students, and helping high performers to achieve their potential
- The department achieved a record A\*- C percentage in my 2nd year

### Summer 2013 - Summer 2016 | Georgeham Football Club Manager | Volunteer

 Produced a motivated, ambitious and committed team, ultimately achieving promotion to the Premier division

#### Education

#### September 2016 - June 2019 | Loughborough University | BSc Mathematics and Sports Science

- Obtained an Upper Second-class degree classification
  - Demonstrated exceptional numerical, analytical and problem-solving skills required in high-level mathematics, often achieving upwards of 70% in mathematics modules
- Demonstrated proficiency in mechanics of sports movements, biomechanics and motor control of sports movements

September 2008 - June 2010 | North Devon College | A-Levels

• Mathematics A | Further Mathematics B | Geography B September 2003 - September 2008 | Braunton School | GCSEs

• 11 A\* - B